hoursguide.com 2019-01-17

# Privacy Policy - Hours Guide

www.hoursguide.com (the Website) collects and manages user data according to the following Privacy Policy. By using the Website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

## Information Collected

The Website servers collect the following information: Internet Protocol (IP) address of computer being used; web pages requested; referring web page; browser used; browser language; date and time; statistics identifying particular IP addresses from which the Website is accessed; and your email address if you have sent us mails or have provided us with your email address.

## Use of Collected Information

The Website uses browser-IP-address information and anonymous-browser history (cookies) to report information about site accesses and for profiling purposes. The information is used to improve Web presentation and utilization. And by collecting your email address, our only goal is to provide you with better services, to send you useful information, to answer your questions, and to respond to your requests.

## Distribution of Collected Information

These aggregated, anonymized data is periodically transmitted to external services to help us improve the Website and service. We currently use Google Analytics (traffic analysis, SEO optimization). Feel free to check out Google’s own Privacy Policies to find out more. Other than this, we will not use the information that we collected for any commercial use; and will not sell any of your personal information, which in this case is your email address specifically, to any third parties or companies.

## Changes to the Privacy Policy

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. A user is bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Services after such changes have been first posted.

If you have any question or concern, please write to contact@hourscenter.com.
